http://www.vailrubber.com/about-us/privacy-policy

Contact Vail
Custom-engineered roll covers that perform better, last longer
Returning your metal, paper or industrial rolls to like-new condition
HomeServicesCustom Engineered CoversRoll MaintenanceHVOF / Thermal SprayOther ServicesIndustriesMetalPaperDiverseAbout VailNewsHistorySafety Mission/VisionPrivacy PolicyOrganizationsContact VailRoll Analysis RequestSearch
Custom Engineered Covers
Get the right cover, finish and profile for your application. Read more
Roll Maintenance
Return your rolls to like-new condition. Read more
HVOF/Thermal Spray
Make parts last 4x longer. Read more
Other Services
Learn how to improve roll performance.. Read more
Metal
Get cost-lowering solutions to your toughest roll problems. Read more
Paper
Significantly increase run times between roll coverings.. Read more
Diverse Solutions
Find ways to efficiently start a new line or cut current costs ... Read more
News
Read about new products, new services, new personnel ... Read more
History
Why our being a family business matters to you ... Read more
Safety Mission/Vision
What you can always count on from VAIL. Read more
Privacy Policy
Committed to protecting your privacy ... Read more
Organizations
Actively participates in a number of industry associations. ... Read more
YoutubeLinkedIn
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Your Privacy
VAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC. respects your privacy. We are particularly sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet and therefore we provide this Privacy Policy so you know about our online information practices and understand how we treat the information we receive about you from the Internet.The Information We CollectIn general, you can browse our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We are however able to determine your IP address. We use your IP address to help administer our website, to measure the use of our website and to improve the content of our website. Our website's registration and contact forms require users to give us contact information (like their names, addresses and email addresses).We use customer contact information from our forms to send the user requested information about our company, our services, tickets and reservation confirmation. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.Personal InformationWe may use your personal information for particular purposes such as processing your order; for marketing research and other marketing purposes; or for providing you with the latest service and promotional information that might be useful to you. We will not give or sell this information to any other company for its use in marketing or solicitation. If you have provided us your personal information and do not wish to receive further information from VAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC., you can send us an email as noted below and tell us that you do not want to receive future communications.Other Important InformationVailrubber.com may contain links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. By using this website you are agreeing to the terms of the Vailrubber.com Privacy Policy.We reserve the right to modify our privacy policy as business needs require. We will post such changes on our website.Contacting the WebsiteIf you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, you can contactWebmasterVail Rubber Works, Inc.521 Langley AvenueP.O. Box 64Saint Joseph, MI 49085877-350-0441This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.Copyright NoticeIn GeneralThis website is provided to you by VAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC. Access to and use of this website and the services available at this website are subject to the following terms and conditions as set forth in this notice. By accessing or using the website or downloading materials from the website, you agree to be legally bound by the terms and conditions set forth below without any modification. Please, review them carefully. If you do not agree to the terms, do not use this website.Copyright and TrademarksCopyright © 2014 VAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC.521 Langley Avenue, Saint Joseph, MI 49085ReservedVAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC. hereby grants to any person the right to reproduce and distribute copies of this work subject to the following conditions:The information found on this website is constantly being updated. Users are responsible for checking the site on a regular basis to keep up with these changes. The publication is to be used for informational purposes only and may not be sold or distributed for commercial gain.The above copyright notice must appear on every copy of the publication or any portion thereof.Except as noted above, no right or license is granted under any copyright, patent, or trademark of VAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC. to any other party.Information contained in this publication is furnished free of charge. Because conditions of use are outside our control, VAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC. makes no warranties, express or implied, and assumes no liability in connection with any use of this information.Electronic Information Submitted to this WebsiteAny communication or material other than your personal information submitted to this website by electronic mail is the exclusive property of VAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC. and is considered to be non-confidential and non-proprietary. Such communication may include without limitation questions, comments, suggestions and ideas. VAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC. shall be free to use them for any purpose whatsoever without restriction or compensation.DisclaimerTHE INFORMATION IN THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTIBILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. VAIL RUBBER WORKS, INC. SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY ERRORS, OMISSIONS OR TECHNICAL INACCURACIES IN THIS WEBSITE.
News About Vail
Pittsburgh AISTech 2019 May 6-9 Booth #2445
Services
Custom Engineered CoversRoll MaintenanceHVOF / Thermal SprayOther Services
Industries
MetalPaperDiverse
About Us
NewsHistorySafety Mission/VisionPrivacy PolicyOrganizations
St. Joseph Service Center
Headquarters521 Langley AvenueSt. Joseph, MI 49085p: 269-983-1595f: 269-983-0155
Mobile Service Center
124 Salco Road EastAxis, AL 36505p: 251-675-5644f: 251-675-5297
Over 100 Years Old
Vail Rubber is an American company that has been owned and operated by the descendants of William A. Vail for more than 100 years. We are also an ISO Certified Company.
The right roll covering solution for your paper, metal or industrial process.
Copyright © 2019 Vail Rubber Co. All Rights Reserved.
Copyright © 2015 Vail Rubber Co. All Rights Reserved.
